Good morning, Nancy.
早上好,Nancy.
Hi, Yvonne. What is that?
你好,Yvonne.那是什么?
It's a box of donuts.
一盒炸面圈.
-Yvonne.  -What?
-Yvonne.  -怎么啦?
Donuts are bad for you.
炸面圈对你身体不好.
But they taste so good. Want one?
但它们味道太好了.来一个吗?
No, I do not want one.
不,我不想要.
Not even a cream-filled donut with chocolate frosting?
奶油馅,上面带巧克力的也不要吗?
There's only one.
只有一个.
I'll get a couple of plates.
我去拿两个盘子.
-Can you hear me?  -Yes.
-能听见我说话吗?   -能.
Libra. Be patient at work.
天秤座.工作要有耐心.
The financial outlook is good.
财运不错.
I like that. What's mine?
真不错.我的呢?
Aries. Stay healthy.
白羊座.保持身体健康.
Now is a good time for a dental check-up.
现在是检查牙齿的好时候.
-A what?   -A dental check-up.
-什么?     -检查牙齿.
Who writes these things?
这些东西是谁写的?
I don't know.
我不知道.
So how are you this morning?
今天早晨好吗?
Fine, except I have to go to a business dinner tonight,
很好,除了今晚有个工作晚餐,
with all of Douglas's real estate colleagues.
和Douglas的房地产公司的同事一起吃饭.
Now, I love my husband.
Now,我爱我的丈夫.
And his co-workers are very nice.
他的同事也都很不错.
But they are all optimists.
但他们全部都是些乐观主义者.
And you're a poor, lonely pessimist.
而你却是一个可怜的,孤独的悲观主义者.
-No.   -Well, I like those dinners.
-不是. -Well,我喜欢那样的晚餐.
Potential clients.
潜在的客户.
Oh, Douglas got us a referral. Klara Kovak.
Oh, Douglas把一个客户推荐给我们.叫Klara Kovak.
-Great.   -She's Hungarian.
-太好了.  -她是个匈牙利人.
-OK.   -It could be a big job, Nancy.
-好.   -这可能是一桩大生意,Nancy.
-Great.  -She's an heiress.
-太好了. -她是位女继承人.
Great.
太好了.